

22 years old, born and raised in the Canary Islands, Spain. Decided to study my degree in England in 2019 and since then I have moved to New York City for my internship year completing a full year on Marketing Research Analysis. Passionate, empathetic, flexible and multifaceted I can be a great reliable asset!

More details about my experience here. Available for phone calls.

Experience

Sales and Marketing Representative – Titanium Marketing Ltd. Leicester, United Kingdom. (February 2023 – May 2023)

- Door to door (D2D) brand ambassador as well as business to customer (B2C) services provided.
- Charity official fundraiser for Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH).
- Customer service mastering.
- Training completed such as sales coaching, personal marketing, objection handling, rapport building.
- Trainer and leader to new recruits.

Marketing Research Junior Analyst – Malaya Services Corporation. New York, New York. (Remotely) (October 2022 – January 2023)

- Independent responsibility with client communications. Specifically presenting reports developed.
- Proficiency managing tabulation plans and tab cross-checking.
- Critical and logical thinking regarding demographic studies. Especially towards consumer studies. Making sure the correct information is portrayed at the best optimal level.
- Market research quantitative analysis by building client-ready reports from findings in surveys data
- Actively engaging with creative ideas, proposing and working on them.
- Flexible working to meet expectations in between the Manila, Philippines office and the New York, New York office.
- Data quality check throughout all stages of the quantitative analysis.

Marketing Research Intern – Malaya Services Corporation. Brooklyn, New York (September 2021 – July 2022)

- Conduct market research activities including data analyses and designing client-facing reports, presentations and other findings.
- Communicating with clients professionally to achieve better results effectively and on the estimated time.
- Proficiency in tracking studies, questionnaire development, and field tracking.
- Report template development for multinational companies such as Google LLC, clients from Jan 2022 - March 2022.
- Experience in posting, reconciling and checking data such as surveys, questionnaires and reports quality check and matching.
- Market research instructor for the rest of the consulting team. Induction into market research analysis.

Client Experience Trainee – Malaya Services Corporation. Brooklyn, New York (September 2021 – July 2022)

- Assistance in client pursuits.
- Preparing business and marketing campaigns.
- Assist clients with Ad Hoc Projects.
- Tracking and compliance of clients' expectations.
- Attendance to client meetings.

Project Manager – Malaya Services Corporation. Brooklyn, New York and Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain. (July 2020 – July 2022)

- Team member scheduling.
- Tracking team progress.
- Strategy Development training.
- Company billing.
- Tracking and compliance of team members' time sheets, team payroll.
- Compliance reporting (official US and Spain documents for governments and official institutions).
- Execute drafts for service manuals.

Resource Manager – Malaya Services Corporation. Brooklyn New York and Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain. (July 2020 – July 2022)

- Human Resources management, Staff and Team Member recruitment.
- Partner firm search and communication.
- Administration of Employee Benefits.
- Employee on-boarding management.
- Draft and review documents as contracts, statement of work and internal and external communications and materials.
- Relocation and cultural support for Team Members.
- Property management, control of issues and matters.

Prominent Individual Family Administrator – Grupo Katigbak, Inc. Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain. (July 2020 – July 2022)

- Effectively employ Design Resolution, Problem Solving and Organizational skills.
- Research properties, valuations, private schools.
- Translator and negotiation with external parties.
- Intermediator towards official institutions (foreigner offices, government and council).
- Household necessities such as utilities set up and staff recruitment.
- Source and evaluate various products and services.
- Self-monitored and reliable reporting functions.

Assistant Team Manager – B'slow Apartments San Agustin. San Bartolomé de Tirajana, Spain. (July 2019 – September 2019)

- In charge of guests' experience.
- Assist meeting calendar dates.
- Carry out the check in for the guests and their information report.
- Room control.
- Assistance with decoration and cleaning.

Education

September 2019 – July 2023 Loughborough University.

Sociology and Criminology Undergraduate Degree. Second Class Honours, Lower Division. Diploma in Professional Studies (International).

Awards and Acknowledgements

Raise and Give (RAG) Highly Commended Award for Event of the Year – Loughborough 2023

"This award recognizes the hard work undertaken by members of the Loughborough Academic Experience community over the past 12 months."

Language certificate from Cambridge - 2019

C1 (Advanced) Level in English Language Certificate

Tools, Applications & Operating System used

- Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word, etc)
- Google Tools (Docs, Sheets, Slides, etc)
- Online Survey Tools

- Zoom / Microsoft Teams / Team Viewer
- macOS / Windows / Linux
- Linkedin.com

Languages

- Spanish Mother language
- English Native written and spoken
- Italian Beginner written and spoken
- Certification on various volunteer/charity activities 2017-2020